It started as a normal day, but
for Mrs. Sharma's husband, it became a fight for his life.
Mrs. Sharma's husband was
suffering from anterior valvular stenosis. To
save his life, immediate surgery was required,
costing ₹20 lakh. Her husband's insurance was
covering the cost of the operation, so Mrs.
Sharma approved the surgery. However,
complications during the surgery
extended his hospital stay, and the total cost
reached ₹1 lakh. His health insurance
covered up to ₹1 lakh, but the Sharma family had to
bear the difference of ₹1 lakh, which became a
huge financial burden during an already stressful time.
Fortunately, they had ICICI Lombard
's Elevate health insurance cover. With its
unlimited sum insured feature,
every expense of ₹1 lakh was fully covered.
Free from financial worries, Mr.
Sharma could focus on his health and family.
You are always covered with Elevate health insurance from ICICI Lombard.
Choose Elevate.